Anyways, I feel like
I can't even go back
and get married to him.
Pretend like
we never have to go back
to America.
I think so.
我想是吧
- I know, I think...
- Did you guys just get here?
你们刚来吗？
Yeah, we... we just
in flew this morning.
对，我们搭今天早上到的飞机
Oh, I'm so jealous.
We leave in a few hours.
好羡慕喔
我们再几个小时就要走了
So, did you have a good time?
你们玩得开心吗？
We had the best time.
Have you guys been here before?
太开心了
－你们以前来过吗？
－没有
No.
饭店很完美，工作人员很贴心
The hotel's perfect,
and the staff is excellent.
－这里的食物很美味
－我听说了
The food is amazing.
- I've heard.
- And the wine. I mean...
还有这里的红酒
We are so excited.
我们很期待
Italy's just so romantic.
Oh, you're gonna die.
意大利太浪漫了
你们会爱死这里
到时打死都不会想离开
They're gonna have
to drag you out of here.
Oh, I'm sure.
我相信一定是这样
Well, I'm gonna get
in the water one last time.
我要在这里最后一次下水了
但是‥
But...
you guys are gonna
have such an amazing trip.
你们一定会玩得很愉快
- Thank you. Nice to meet you.
- Thanks.
谢谢‥
－幸会
－祝你们回程平安
- You too.
- Safe travels.
－谢谢
－再见‥
- Thanks. Bye!
- Bye!
Oh, what the fuck was that?
什么东西？
Holy fuck.
Oh, my fucking God.
天啊‥
Holy fucking shit.
Help! Help! Help! Help!
救命‥
Help! Help!
Help!
Valentina.
－瓦伦蒂娜　－你干吗一脸凝重？
有一位房客溺毙了
什么？
没事，大海不在饭店范围内
爱奥尼亚海的事故我们不负责
你不懂
沙尔瓦多说还有其他尸体
其他尸体？
罗可，有其他尸体是什么意思？
还有其他房客遭到杀害
罗可，总共死了几个房客？
我不知道‥
好几个吧？
该死
You must stay behind there.
请不要靠近
＂一周前＂
你好啊
- Allora!
- Oh.
米亚
Mia.
你怎么了？
Huh?
马西莫交新女友了
你还放不下马西莫？
别再想了
走啦，船到了
－什么船？　－跟我来
（意语）晚点再见
（意语）我再打给你
Sì!
（意语）我们要去哪里？
所有人挥右手打招呼
香槟‥
为什么盘子这么小？
罗可，有十位客人，这盘子太小了
你觉得这样正常吗？
拿什么小盘子‥
罗可，我们晚点要聊聊
你让我很难做事
－你知道他长怎样吗？　－不知道
他说会搭十二点到的船
谁都有可能
不会是那个老人家吧？
我觉得不是
你以前接过这么老的吗？
－他们还能‥　－当然能
有时候得喂他们吃药
恶心，露西
Signori Di Grasso.
狄格拉索先生
欢迎来到白莲花大饭店
Welcome to the White Lotus.
I am Valentina,
the resort manager.
我是饭店经理瓦伦蒂娜
- Ah.
- How was your boat ride?
－搭船来的路上怎么样？
－太美了
It was bellissimo.
I mean, I'm impressed
that you are even here.
我很佩服你能来到这里
Why are you impressed?
这话怎么说？
It's a long trip
from Los Angeles,
洛杉矶离这里很远
and you are quite old, no?
你已经很老了，不是吗？
Anyway, Isabella here
will take you up to the hotel...
总之，伊莎贝拉
会带你到漂亮的房间
and bring you
to your beautiful rooms.
Can I offer you
a glass of Prosecco?
要来杯薄赛珂气泡酒吗？
Oh. Thank you, dear.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
谢谢你，亲爱的
看到你我精神都来了
Thank you.
－谢谢，请往这里走
－干杯
- Cheers.
- This way.
- Thank you.
- You like it?
－喜欢吗？
－喜欢，谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
你好，亲爱的
Hello, darling.
Oh.
那两个还不错
Hey. Welcome to Sicily.
欢迎来到西西里
真帅
不好了
Mr. and Mrs. Sullivan.
苏利文夫妻
他们都是跟老婆来的
反正也不是第一次
You must be
Mr. and Mrs. Spiller?
你们一定是史匹勒夫妻吧？
男人真令人失望
How was your flight?
－航程顺利吗？
－还可以
- It was fine.
- Yeah.
卡麦隆的行李在罗马搞丢了
But they did lose
Cameron's bag in Rome.
Oh, never transfer through Rome.
Fiumicino always loses bags.
绝对别在罗马转机
罗马机场老是搞丢旅客行李
Oh.
You should have
flown through Munich.
你们应该从慕尼黑飞过来的
- Thanks for the tip.
- Yeah. Next time.
－谢谢告知
－下次就知道了
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
－不客气
－谢谢
来点意大利薄赛珂酒？
Please, some Italian Prosecco?
- Let's toast, people.
- No, thanks.
－来敬酒吧
－我不用
- I think I'll just wait.
- Harper... You don't want one?
－我等等再喝
－哈珀，你不来一杯吗？
No. I don't want one.
对，我不想喝
- They wanna do a toast.
- Can you hold the glass for me?
－他们想敬酒，做个样子就好
－我六小时没吃东西了
I haven't eaten in six hours.
- I don't need any more drinks.
- Sorry.
－我不要喝酒
－抱歉
Just hold it.
拿着杯子就好
- Sorry.
- That's okay.
对不起
－没关系
－干杯，我们到了
- Cheers. We made it.
- Cheers.
欢迎来到西西里白莲花大饭店
Welcome
to the White Lotus in Sicily.
Mm. Thank you.
If your bag will ever arrive,
如果你的行李到了
我们会马上通知
- we'll let you know right way.
- Okay.
－好
－如果你相信有奇迹的话
If you believe in miracles.
Okay, thank you.
－好，谢谢你
－不客气
You're welcome.
So, you don't like Prosecco?
你不喜欢薄赛珂酒吗？
- No, no, it's fine. Thank you.
- Yeah.
－没这回事，谢谢你
－好
- Okay. Okay. Thank you.
- Okay, careful.
好‥
－请小心
－谢谢
Ah! Ah! Oh.
Mrs. McQuoid-Hunt!
麦瓦杭特小姐
Ooh.
她的行李也太多了
Welcome
to the White Lotus in Sicily.
欢迎来到西西里白莲花大饭店
也许她要搬到意大利
You guys just really...
你们真是太棒了，是真的
Just pull out all the stops.
You really do.
Whenever I stay
at a White Lotus,
每次住白莲花大饭店
I always have
a memorable time. Always.
都让我留下深刻的回忆
每次都是
您是我们非常重视的花朵会员
And you are
in our Blossom Circle.
So, you are
very important to us.
Mm. But I was a Petal,
我本来是花瓣会员
and I've worked
my way up to Blossom. Yeah.
后来才努力升上花朵会员
You know that your husband
is already here?
您的丈夫已经到了，您知道吗？
Good. Because...
那太好了‥因为他没回我讯息
he hasn't been responding
to my texts.
Shall we?
－走吧
－好
Yeah, okay. Okay,
Portia, do you get service here?
－波蒂亚，你手机有讯号吗？
－有，我们应该都有吧
Yeah, I think
we both have full service.
Maybe we could take it
to AT&T or something.
可以去通讯行问问
Wow.
这家饭店也太棒了
This hotel is so cool.
这里原本是修道院
Well, originally,
it was a convent.
Honey, check out this view.
老婆，你看这个景
- Whoa. Is that a volcano?
- Mount Etna.
－那是火山吗？
－埃特纳火山
Hey, what is with these
head things?
这些头是什么？
We keep seeing them everywhere.
到处都是
Testa di Moro.
摩尔人头像
- Testa di Moro?
- Yeah. Well, the story is
－摩尔人头像？
－是的，有一个故事
a Moor came here a long time ago
and seduced a local girl.
很久以前，一个摩尔人来到这里
诱惑了一个本地少女
But then she found out
that he had a wife
后来她发现他在家乡有老婆小孩
and children back home.
她不甘心受骗
所以把他的头砍了下来
So, because he lied to her,
she cut his head off.
- Oh.
- Jesus.
天啊
So if you put one
of those outside of your house,
把这种头像放在
家门口有什么含意？
what are you saying?
If you come into my house,
don't fuck my wife.
警告客人不准上我老婆
是警告丈夫不准乱搞
否则会被杀了埋在后院
It's a warning
to husbands, babe.
Screw around and you'll end up
buried in the garden.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, before I forget.
差点忘了，我要介绍
这个房间的特色
I'll show you a special feature.
- Cool.
- If I open this door,
－好啊
－这扇门打开可以连通两个房间
you can connect the two rooms.
- Should I show you?
- Oh! Yeah, cool.
－要我示范吗？
－不用了
No, no, that's okay.
I doubt we'll use that.
我们应该用不上
Okay.
好吧
I mean, it's possible
at some point. I don't know.
也许能用上吧，我也不知道
多个选项也不错吧？
It's good to have
the option, yeah?
－是啊
－也对
- Yeah.
You never know.
谁知道呢？
- Guys, we did it!
- Yeah!
各位，我们到了
－是啊
－我们终于来了
Come on! We're finally here!
We've been talking
about this forever.
说要来已经很久了，这太棒了
This is awesome. Oh!
I'm so happy we're here.
－我好高兴我们来了
－一定会很好玩
- It's gonna be great.
- Yeah.
Yeah, totally.
你们说得对
- Let me show you your rooms.
- Yeah!
－我带你们去房间吧
－好
Let's go.
－这边请
－晚点见了
You go first. All right, guys.
See you later.
Yeah. See you.
再见
干吗？
What?
Oh. I should tell you.
我要告诉你
Both my parents
were born in Sicily.
－我的父母都是在西西里出生的
－这样啊
- Oh.
- Yeah, they came
他们小时候就移民到美国了
to the States as children.
Yeah, so we are Sicilian,
但我们跟你一样是西西里人
just like you.
Although I'm not from Sicily.
I am from Milan.
但我不是西西里人，我来自米兰
Oh, you do have more
of a Northern look.
你确实长得比较像北方人
有漂亮的淡褐色眼睛
Beautiful hazel eyes.
Wonderful smile.
而且笑容很美
- You're very kind.
- You must be very popular.
谢谢夸奖
你一定很受欢迎吧
- All right, Dad.
- Ah.
爸，好了
Anyway, we're here because
we're gonna visit the town
总之，我们此行的目的
是拜访我奶奶以前住的地方
- my grandmother's from.
- Oh!
It's a little town,
uh, Testa dell'Acqua.
一个叫特斯塔德阿瓜的小镇
Yeah, that sounds very special.
感觉很有意义
Hopefully, um,
we can find some people there
我们希望能在那里找到会说英语的人
who can speak English, you know,
帮我们寻找一些远房亲戚
maybe help us track down
some distant relatives.
'Cause we definitely
don't speak Italian.
因为我们不会讲意语
Oh, you should come, Isabella.
伊莎贝拉，你可以当我们的翻译
You could be our translator.
We need you.
我们需要你
- Dad.
- Hmm?
爸，别烦人家了
Leave her alone.
We'll take it from here.
－接下来我们自己来就行了
－谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
Shall I show you how
to close the curtains?
要教你们怎么关窗帘吗？
There's a button
over there on the...
－有一个按钮‥
－没关系，我们会自己摸索
That's okay.
We'll figure it out.
我想知道
按钮在哪里，伊莎贝拉？
I'd like to know.
Where is this button, Isabella?
Dad! I'm gonna help
you find it, okay?
爸，我会帮你找，好吗？
- Thank you very, very much.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
－非常感谢你
－谢谢你
- Thank you.
- You're very lovely.
－谢谢
－你很美
Thank you.
－谢谢你
－有你这样的员工是他们的福气
They are lucky
to have you working here.
Be our translator...
来当我们的翻译‥
You slammed the door
in that poor girl's face!
你在人家面前关门
那么大力干吗？
You were harassing her.
是你在骚扰人家
- How? I was not.
- You kinda were. And farting.
－我才没有呢
－我觉得有，还在她面前放屁
It's the Prosecco.
都是薄赛珂酒害的
Okay. Albie and I
are gonna go to our rooms.
我和阿尔比要回房间了
We'll come back for you
in a bit. You gonna be okay?
我们晚点再来找你
你没问题吧？
－我‥
－那就好
- Uh...
- Great.
Why did we do this?
我们为什么要来？
It's nice, Dad.
It's a nice thing to do.
这是好事，爸
这是好事一件
I got a migraine.
I'm gonna go lay down.
我头好痛，先去躺一下
Okay. Well, I'm probably
gonna head down to the pool.
好‥
我想去游泳池
Um, and then what time
did you wanna meet up for...
你要几点集合‥
The most ancient art
is 14th century.
最古老的艺术品来自十四世纪
- Oh, my God. Really?
- Yeah. Oh.
天啊，哪里‥
您失踪的老公在这里
- Your missing husband is here.
- Oh!
- Oh, ho!
- Hey.
Hi!
- How was the flight? Mm.
- I missed you so much.
路上还顺利吗？
Hey, uh, yeah, you know
I texted you a bunch of times.
我传了好几次讯息给你
And you never texted me back.
但你都没回我
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
我知道，对不起
工作发生紧急事件‥
We just had a flare-up
at work, it was...
要帮你们介绍房间吗？
还是说‥
Shall I show
you your room, or...
Oh. Yeah, definitely.
好啊
What the hell is she doing here?
－她来做什么？
－什么？
What?
Yeah, uh, well, look.
听着，我自己出门旅行‥
I'm traveling by myself...
你跟老公度假还要带助理？
You bring your assistant
to a vacation with your husband?
有任何需要都可以到那里找我
Anything you need,
I'll be there. Okay?
Well, I just don't know
what the big deal is.
我不懂，这有什么大不了的？
I mean, I don't know
why you're so bothered.
你干吗大惊小怪？
因为我叫你别带她来
Because I said no!
Because it's supposed
to be romantic.
因为这应该是一场浪漫之旅
Because it's a vacation,
in Sicily, for us.
我们在西西里共度两人时光
I mean it's...
可是‥
I mean,
it's not like she's, like,
她又不会跟我们睡同一张床
gonna be in our bed
and stuff, you know?
- I mean, she has her own room.
- Tanya.
－她有自己的房间
－谭雅
Get rid of her.
－把她赶走
－好啦，我会把她赶走‥
All right, I'll get rid of her.
I'll get rid of her. All right?
－满意了吗？
－让她搭飞机回家
- All right.
- Put her on a plane.
Hey. Um...
You're gonna have to get lost.
你必须离开
好‥
Okay. Yeah.
So, what do you mean?
I'd see you in a week, then?
所以‥我们下周再见吗？
不对‥我要你留在附近
No, no, no, no.
I want you to stay... stay close,
'cause I might need you.
But just lay low
因为我可能会需要你
但你要保持低调，不要离开房间
and... and not come out
of your room. Okay?
I gotta go. I gotta go!
我得走了‥
我叫她走了‥
I did it. I did it.
Oh. Hi, Portia.
你好，波蒂亚
Do you want a drink?
－你要喝点东西吗？
－我饿了
I'm hungry.
这里有点心
Well, we have these
little... little things here.
I just think it's like,
我只是觉得
你把公司卖了，赚了一堆钱
you sold your company,
you got rich,
他就突然和你称兄道弟？
and now he's your best friend?
That's just...
这真是‥你要睡那一边吗？
Are you taking
that side of the bed?
I always sleep on that side.
可是我习惯睡那边
Okay. Which is it a big deal?
好，这件事很重要吗？
Yeah, I wanna sleep
on my side of the bed.
对，我想睡我习惯的那边
Okay.
I'll sleep over there.
好，那我睡另一边
Yeah, I think that's better.
这样比较好
Also, they're so
touchy-feely. Right?
而且他们一直卿卿我我
你发现了吗？
Like, do you notice that?
It feels performative.
很像在表演给人看，有谁会那样？
- Like, who does that?
- Happily married couples?
婚姻幸福的夫妻？
Couples that have been
married for five years?
但他们已经结婚五年了
No way. It feels fake.
我觉得是演的
You're so quick to judge people.
你真爱批评别人
Yeah, people that brag
about taking helicopters
他们吹嘘搭直升机到汉普顿
跟杰夫贝佐斯当朋友
to the Hamptons
and being friends
with Jeff Bezos. I mean...
只要你能忍受
跟卡麦隆相处五分钟
Look, Cameron
is the kinda guy who,
if you can put up
with him for five minutes,
you can put up with him forever.
He is consistent.
就能跟他做一辈子的朋友
他至少始终如一
始终如一的混帐吗？
A consistent douche?
没错
Yeah. He's crazy, it's funny.
他是个疯子，而且很好笑
- Was he like that in college?
- Way worse.
他在大学时就是这样吗？
比现在更糟糕
Why were you
even friends with him?
你为什么会和他当朋友？
We weren't friends,
we were roommates.
我们一开始只是室友
And then, you know how it is.
你也懂的，我们越来越熟
You kind of become friends,
and now we're friends.
于是就成为朋友了
At some point,
he is gonna approach you
他一定会找时间
跟你推销赚钱的方法
with some kind
of money-making scheme
or some kind of favor
or something.
或者想叫你帮个忙
There's a reason
they invited us here.
他们邀请我们一定有原因
Well, that's my prediction.
So, we'll see.
这是我的预测，就看准不准吧
Can you just please
try to make an effort?
你能不能试着开心一点？
Or else this is gonna
be a very awkward week.
否则这一周的气氛会很僵
When do I ever
make things awkward?
我何时把气氛搞僵了？
Could you put these...
These are hers.
这些是她的东西
放在沙发上或其他地方
Just put them on the couch
or the... anywhere. Thank you.
谢谢你‥
Grazie! Thank you!
（意语）
马可，我是瓦伦蒂娜
等我一下‥罗可
你想喝杯茶吗？
我刚说到‥
我很不满，２２２号房的房客
反应在衣柜发现一条湿抹布
等一下
你们两个，等一下
Hey!
需要什么吗？
我们来找一位房客
叫什么名字？
他是美国人
这里有很多美国人，名字呢？
他叫汤姆克鲁斯
饭店只允许房客进出
安东尼欧
送这两位小姐出去
我认得你们，知道你们来干吗
－不准在我的饭店胡搞　－你嫉妒吗
你连欢愉也不懂，看脸就知道了
至少我不必出卖身体
谁要花钱买你的身体？
你这放不开的丑婆娘
为什么没人把入口看好？
出口也是
What?
怎样？
Well, we got here in one piece.
我们安全抵达了
My dad's not in the best shape
我爸的状况不好
而且他已经开始惹我生气了
and he's already getting
on my nerves, but...
I'm in the middle
of something, Dom, okay?
我在忙，阿多
- I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
－我要挂了
－好
Um, well...
我今天想到你
这趟是我们一起规划的
I was thinking of you. You know?
We planned this together
and I, uh,
我很希望你能一起来
just really wish you were here.
Yeah, right.
Okay. Whatever, Dom.
对啦，随便你怎么说
No. Not whatever.
我不是随便说说的
你就是，别烦我了
Yes, whatever.
Just fuck off!
好吧
Okay. Um,
listen, Cara is not answering
my calls.
卡拉不接我电话
Well, she doesn't want
to talk to you, so,
她不想跟你说话
我也不知道怎么说
I... I don't know.
Well, you should
encourage her to talk to me.
你应该劝她跟我说话
You know what? I'm not
getting involved in that.
我才不要淌这滩浑水
但你已经插手了
不然她为什么要生我的气？
But you are getting involved,
or why else would
she be mad at me?
Because of this latest
fucking bullshit, Dom!
因为你最近做的烂事
And everything else over
the last ten fucking years!
还有过去十年来的所有烂事
Do you really think you
should be telling her all this?
你觉得应该跟她说这些吗？
有何不可？
丢脸的人又不是我
Why not?
I have nothing to be ashamed of!
And I'm honest.
而且我很诚实，不会隐瞒家人
I don't keep fucking secrets
from my family!
You should try it sometime!
你应该好好学习
Well, Albie's here.
He's not upset.
阿尔比来了，他就不气我
他当然气你
Yes, he fucking is!
He's just... he just doesn't want
to fight you.
他只是不想跟你吵
He's a sweet,
sensitive young man.
他是个贴心敏感的年轻人
And I honestly don't know
how it happened.
我不知道你怎么
会有他那样的儿子
Sure as hell
didn't get it from you.
肯定没有遗传到你
Okay. Jesus. Um...
好啦，老天
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
对不起，发生这么多事
And I still love you...
－我还是爱着你‥
－你给我闭嘴，阿多
Shut the fuck up, Dom.
Shut up with the fucking
sorrys already, okay? Enough!
不要再说你很抱歉了
已经够了
Okay.
好吧
I'll let you know
how it all goes.
－我再告诉你这里顺不顺利
－我不在乎，阿多
I don't fucking care, Dom!
I've wasted enough of my life.
我已经浪费了太多人生
I don't want you
calling me anymore!
你不要再打给我了
Oh, my God, please.
It's fucking done! Okay?
请你放过我，我们结束了
好吗？
别再烦我了
Leave me alone.
Seriously! Fuck you!
我说真的
你这王八蛋烂货去死一死吧
Go fuck yourself. You fucking
piece of fucking shit!
This is such a fucked situation.
I feel like I've just been stuck
我真是太惨了
我这三年来一直困在家里
滑手机看负面新闻
at home, just doom-scrolling
on my phone
the last three years,
and I finally get out
of there...
现在我终于走出家门来到意大利
and I'm in Italy,
and she just told me
that I have to stay in my room
她却叫我不要离开房间
the whole time!
They're both fucking psycho.
他们两个都是疯子
It's fucked! Like,
the job is a joke!
这是哪门子工作啊？
那就辞职吧
- Then quit.
- She's a f... She's a mess.
她整个人一团乱，很可悲
She's a miserable mess.
If I had a half
a billion dollars,
如果我有一亿美元
I would not be miserable.
I would be enjoying my life!
我才不会跟她一样惨
我会好好享受人生
It's... so unfair,
and I'm so tired.
真是太不公平了，我觉得好累
Oh, don't worry about her.
别管她了，去找人上床吧
Just go get some dick.
I know! That's...
I know! That's what I...
我知道‥我也是这样想
That's what I wanted.
I wanna do...
我也想找个意大利帅哥滚床单
get thrown around
by some hot Italian guy,
and now I'm just gonna be
sitting in my room eating pasta.
现在我只能在房里吃意大利面
The menu's all pasta!
I'm gonna be so bloated.
菜单上全都是意大利面
我一定会变得很肿，讨厌死了
- This sucks.
- Oh, shit. Portia.
糟糕，波蒂亚，我得去工作了
- Portia, I gotta get to work.
- Oh, right. Okay.
好
Love you.
－爱你
－我也爱你，再传讯息给你
- Love you. Text you later.
- Bye!
再见‥
Bye.
Hey, Harper, I just realized.
哈珀，我突然发现
我认识你法学院的同学
I know someone
that knows you from law school.
Uh, Kevin Kourepenos.
He actually says hi.
凯文柯皮诺
他要我跟你打招呼
你要我也跟他问好吗？
Do you want me to say hi?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Um, tell him I said hi,
好啊‥
请帮我跟他问好
恭喜他没被吊销律师执照
and congrats
on not getting disbarred.
Okay. I'll tell him.
好，我会告诉他的
So, you do employment law.
So interesting.
你专攻劳动法，真有趣
Mm-hmm.
What is that exactly?
劳动法是什么？
Um, we, you know,
我们帮助委托人控告雇主
we take on clients
that are suing their employers
for discrimination,
sexual harassment,
他们可能遭到歧视
性骚扰，非法解雇等等
wrongful termination,
stuff like that.
真有趣
Amazing.
- What? What is that face?
- No, no, no.
－那是什么表情？
－没事，只是‥
Nothing. Just, um...
We've been dealing
我们最近遇到一些不实指控
with a bunch
of bogus claims lately.
所有人都一样
- I mean, everyone has.
- Ah! Hmm.
I mean, even when they
have zero merit
尽管这些指控毫无依据
会在简易判决中遭到驳回
and they get thrown out
in summary judgment,
you still have to go through
all the depos
还是得提供证词，面临内部调查
and the internal investigations.
非常耗费时间
更别提浪费多少钱了，天啊
It's a total time suck.
Not to mention a huge waste
of money. I mean...
God.
Mm.
并非全部都是不实指控
Well, they're not all bogus.
－是啊
－你说得对，糟糕
- No.
- No! God, no. Fuck.
Of course they're not.
当然是这样
Harper, no,
of course they're not.
－哈珀，你说得没错，对不起
－没关系‥
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no. It's fine.
抱歉
Sorry.
All good.
没事
I bet you're really tough.
你一定很厉害
I bet your clients
are really happy
委托人一定很高兴有你的支持
to have you in their corner.
是啊，我可不想跟你作对
Yeah. God,
wouldn't wanna mess with you.
She's like the star of her firm.
Wins every case.
她是事务所的大明星
所有案件都胜诉
Of course you are.
那是当然的了
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
我没事，我只是在烦恼‥
I... I just am dealing
with some...
work stuff.
工作的事情
It's... It's nothing.
It's dumb...
没事的，谢谢你的关心
Thank you for asking.
I think I saw you
and your cute grandfather
我好像在船上看过你
和你可爱的爷爷
on the boat on the way in.
－我也看过你
－这样啊
- Yeah. I... I saw you, too.
- Yeah.
－我是波蒂亚
－阿尔比
- I'm Portia.
- Albie.
- Hey. Yeah.
- Hey.
- Where are you from?
- Los Angeles.
－你是哪里人？
－洛杉矶
- Cool.
- Yeah. What about you?
－真酷
－你呢？
San Francisco.
旧金山
I love San Francisco.
It's beautiful.
我爱旧金山，那里很美
Yeah. Yeah.
是啊‥
I... I actually spent
a lot of time there
我常待在旧金山
因为我念附近的学校
because I went
to a school nearby.
Oh, yeah? What school?
哪所学校？
I... went to... Stanford.
我读‥史丹福
不要觉得丢脸
Don't be so ashamed.
Wha... I... I'm not, it's just...
我不觉得丢脸，只是‥
I went to Chico State, so...
我念加州州大溪口分校
Oh, cool.
真酷
是啊，真酷
Yeah. "Cool."
Cool.
真酷
- Uh, what do you do now?
- Um, for work?
你现在做什么？
你是指工作吗？
Yeah.
－对
－我‥
I... I act... I work
for this company
我在都市计划顾问公司上班
that does urban
planning consulting.
Hmm.
我还只是实习生
I'm just an intern
at this point, so...
So you can go
on vacation for a week
所以可以放一周的假
没有人在乎
- and no one gives a shit.
- Basically. Yeah.
大致上是这样没错
Oh. There's your grandfather.
你爷爷在那里，他真的好可爱
He's truly such an adorable man.
Yeah. He's a lot...
是啊‥他很特别
My dad and I brought him here
because we're Sicilian...
我爸和我带他来这里
我们是西西里人
应该说我们的祖先是
Or we have Sicilian heritage.
Um, our last name's Di Grasso.
我们姓狄格拉索
And we're taking him
to the town where his, um,
我们要带他去他祖母出生的小镇
grandmother was born.
真酷，这样真好
Cool. That's... so nice.
Oh, my God!
天啊，你爷爷跌倒了
Your grandfather just fell!
Oh, no.
－不好了
－爷爷‥你还好吗？
- Nonno!
- Nonno, are you okay?
- Huh?
- You okay?
－你还好吗？
－我没事‥我绊倒了
- Yeah, no, no. I'm fine. I...
- Sir?
I tripped.
你有没有伤到头？
Did you hit your head or anything?
Oh, my gosh.
－天啊，你的手
－没事啦‥
- No, no. No, no.
- Your hand, it's...
- It's fine, it's fine.
- Are you okay?
－你还好吗？
－没事，亲爱的，谢谢你
Uh, oh, no, darling, thank you.
- Hello.
- Hi.
你好‥
Are you... are you sure
you're good?
你真的没事吗？
你跌倒了，我很担心
I mean, I'm so sorry you fell.
我只是来看风景的
Just came to see the view,
I mean...
爷爷，我陪你走
那边有好风景，走吧
Yeah, I'll...
I'll walk with you, Nonno.
- There's a good view this way. Come on.
- Huh? Okay.
Oh, my hat.
－我的帽子
－我来捡‥
Oh, I'll get... Yeah. Oh.
Yeah.
好
- Here you go.
- Okay.
－之后再见了
－好，我‥
Uh, maybe I'll see you around.
- Yeah. Yeah, I'll... I'm just...
- Okay.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
－我没事‥
－我要去喝点东西
- Gonna get a drink.
- Who's the girl?
那个女生是谁？
Hi.
Right now?
现在吗？
Hey, where you going?
你要去哪里？
Oh, don't you want me
to wash up first?
你不要我先洗个澡吗？
It's hot out!
外头很热，我的跨下跟沼泽一样
I got swamp crotch.
Yeah.
God, he's always thinking of me.
他真会为我着想
Totally disregard
my text about the Ambien.
不用理会我问安眠药的讯息
我已经找到了
I have located my Ambien.
－天啊，真是好消息
－谢天谢地
- Oh, my gosh! I'm so glad.
- Thank God.
'Cause we don't have any,
so I'm sorry about that.
因为我们没有，真是抱歉
真的吗？
你们没在吃安眠药？
Oh. Really? You guys
don't take sleeping pills?
No.
－没有
－从来没吃过？
- Ever?
- Nope.
从来没有
- You have trouble sleeping?
- Mm.
你有睡眠困扰吗？
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
－对
－你为什么睡不着？
Why?
Why can't you sleep?
Just, like work stuff?
因为工作的关系吗？
Yeah, but also just...
是啊，还有‥
I don't know, just
everything that's going on...
我也不知道
世界上正在发生的一切
in the world.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
什么意思，什么事情？
Oh, I don't know. Just,
like, the end of the world.
我不知道，感觉世界要毁灭了
Oh. No, Harper!
Oh, come on!
－不是吧，哈珀
－拜托
世界没有要毁灭，情况没那么糟
The world's not ending,
it's not that bad.
Honestly, Cam and I don't even
watch the news anymore.
－我跟小卡已经不看新闻了
－是啊
Yeah.
- You don't follow the news?
- No.
－你们不看新闻？
－是啊
- What?
- Like, I'm just so over
－什么？
－我已经受够新闻轮播了
the whole news cycle, you know?
It's... it's like, gimme a break.
－请放过我吧
－他们想吓坏所有人
They're just trying
to freak everybody out.
Yeah. They're just polarizing
society by making us
他们希望我们对末日闹剧上瘾
借此分化社会
glued to their apocalyptic
soap opera, you know?
- It's like...
- Yeah. And even if it was
是啊，就算情况真有那么糟糕
as bad as they say it is,
- I mean what can you really do, you know?
- Right.
我们有什么办法？
我们会投票，捐钱
不能想太多
We vote, we donate money.
You can't obsess.
你真的会投票吗？
说实话，老婆
- Did you vote, babe? Be honest.
- I did.
我投了
Doesn't matter.
算了
I voted. Didn't I?
我投啦，没有吗？
我觉得你没投
- I don't think you did.
- I think I did. I did.
我明明就投了
I don't know.
我可不确定
Mm. Okay, so you guys
don't watch the news.
好，所以你们不看新闻
Um... What do you do,
like, all day?
那你们一整天都做什么？
Oh. Well, I mean,
I'm... I'm home with the kids.
－我主要都在家带小孩
－当然了‥
- I mean, mostly. Yep.
- Oh, right. Of course. Right.
We do a lot of Dateline.
我常看＂日界线＂
I love it.
Husbands murdering their wives.
我好爱那个节目
好多丈夫杀害自己的妻子
Happens a lot on vacation.
他们常在度假时下手
例如潜水的时候
Scuba diving.
He'll just unplug her oxygen
while she's underwater.
趁老婆在水下的时候拔掉氧气管
Happens more than you think.
其实很常发生
Why... why are you looking at me?
看我干吗？
为什么我们都在看你？
Why are we all looking at you?
Yeah.
卡麦隆喜欢看阳刚的实境节目
Cameron really likes
to watch macho reality TV.
The guys are really ugly.
那些人很丑
Oh, my God. That sounds
so bad, but they are.
天啊，这样说感觉很不对
但事实如此
Honey, the people on Dateline
＂日界线＂的人也不怎么好看
aren't exactly
attractive either.
At least
they're murdering each other.
至少他们会彼此残杀
伊森，你都看什么？
What do you watch, Ethan?
Uh, what do we watch?
Like, documentaries.
我们都看什么‥纪录片
Ted Lasso, sometimes.
偶尔会看＂泰德拉索＂
- We love Ted Lasso.
- Love Ted Lasso. Gotta.
我们很爱＂泰德拉索＂
- Mm.
- Oh, you like it?
－你们喜欢吗？
－当然了
- Yeah, man.
- Yes, of course.
－他很讨喜，对吧？
－我没看
- So likable, right?
- Yeah.
- I don't watch Ted Lasso.
- No?
－我超喜欢
－是吗？
- Yeah, such a good guy.
- Yeah.
－他真是个好人
－是啊
So much content now. It's like
there's billions of shows,
现在的节目太多了
我们好像永远追不上
everyone's trying to keep up.
－有点令人窒息
－节目太多了‥
It's kinda suffocating, honestly.
Yeah. Too much.
It's too much.
It's like we're all
感觉我们忙着娱乐彼此
放任世界毁灭，对吧？
entertaining each other
while the world burns, right?
We're all just zombies, you
know, like...
我们就像活尸一样
Hmm.
I love a binge.
我喜欢追剧
I don't. Yeah...
我不喜欢，你呢？
Anyway.
－总之‥
－好的
Okey dokey. Well...
如果不能游泳
起码要做个日光浴吧
if I can't get a swim in,
I may as well get a tan, right?
Hey, you know you can
just borrow one of my suits.
－我可以借你一件泳裤
－好啊‥
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'd love a swim-in.
我很想游泳，太好了
- That'd be great.
- Yeah?
Weren't you gonna go up to
get some sunscreen anyway?
你是不是要上楼拿防晒乳？
- Oh, yeah.
- You could grab it for him.
－对喔
－可以帮他拿泳裤吗？
Oh, yeah. I'll come up
with you actually,
我跟你一起上去吧，顺便换一换
'cause I gotta change
into it anyway.
- Another round of Spritzes, E?
- Sure, I'm on it!
再来一轮开胃酒吗？
好，我去点
还要喝？
Another round?
他喜欢在喝完前点下一杯
Yeah, he likes to order
'em before they're gone.
Yeah.
What are you...
What the fuck?
搞什么啊？
Oh, my God.
天啊
I... I... I must have
been disassociating.
我一定是解离了
I was seeing
all these faces of men
我看到许多男人的脸
with these very
effeminate hairstyles.
他们留着非常阴柔的发型
然后‥
And then...
我看到你
I saw you,
and your eyes were
like shark eyes,
你的眼睛跟鲨鱼一样
like just completely dead.
死气沉沉的‥
Just like, dead.
Well, you really know
how to pump a guy up.
你真懂得取悦男人
Must've been the Bonine
that I took before the flight.
一定是因为我搭机前吃了晕机药
我还没高潮
I didn't get to finish.
I need to take a breather.
我需要休息一下
Making love
In the afternoon with Tanya...
下午跟谭雅做爱就是这样
Tanya?
谭雅
什么事？
Yeah?
You ate all
the macaroons, didn't you?
你把蛋白杏仁饼吃完了，对吧？
What macaroons?
什么蛋白杏仁饼？
How do you expect
to lose weight if you inhale
你吃了五颗蛋白杏仁饼
是要怎么减重？
five macaroons
and not even remember?
还立刻忘记
There were only three.
原本只有三颗
There were five.
明明有五颗
香槟也是你喝的吗？
Did you drink
the champagne, too?
I think he put them in here.
应该放在这里
Yeah.
－找到了
－我试穿看看
- Oh, washing bag?
- Yes.
Hey, uh, listen.
听着
I know we don't know
each other that well,
我知道我们不熟
but I really appreciate you
being here.
但我很感激你来这趟
You know, it means a lot.
这对我很重要
以前伊森没什么女人缘
Ethan never really
brought around a lot of girls,
so I'm just so happy
that he found someone.
他找到对象我很高兴
I think it's great.
真是太好了
Well, thanks for inviting us.
－谢谢你邀我们
－没什么
Sure.
－这周一定会很好玩
－没错
- It'll be fun.
- It will be.
- I'm gonna get the sunscreen.
- Yeah.
－我去拿防晒乳
－好
Hey.
- Hey!
- What do you think?
你觉得如何？
是不是有点紧？
Little snug, right?
－我觉得可以
－是吗？
I think they're fine.
Yeah? Hmm.
Can't find the sunscreen.
我找不到防晒乳
You know what? They probably
have a bunch of that
游泳池边应该有很多
by the pool.
- I'm gonna keep looking.
- Yeah.
－我再找找看
－好啊
- Hey, I'll see you down there.
- Hmm.
楼下见
- Hi.
- Hey, um,
爷爷在泳池边跌倒了
Nonno fell by the pool.
- What?
- He's fine. Um,
－什么？
－他没事
but I think he hit his head.
He could have a concussion.
但我觉得他撞到头了
他有可能脑震荡
I'm thinking someone
should sleep with him tonight.
我觉得今晚应该
要有人陪他睡，以防万一
- Keep an eye on him.
- Yeah. Good idea.
好主意，就让他到你房间睡
Um...
Uh, we'll put him in your room.
我得工作
洛杉矶那边的人还醒着
I got work stuff. L.A. will
still be up. I'm gonna be up
我整晚都不能睡
and around all night.
So let's just, uh...
所以今晚让他跟你睡，好吗？
We'll put him
in your room. Okay?
Okay.
好
- Anything else?
- No.
－还有事吗？
－没了
What do you say, dinner at 8:00?
－八点吃晚餐好吗？
－好
- Yeah. Sure.
- All right.
就这样
这家伙真讨厌
露西，他怎么找到你的？
网路，我有一个专页
有人在ＩＧ上私讯我
要用五十欧元买我的脚照
当时我才发现我随时都能赚大钱
Hmm.
我们一起三人行吧
－可以收他双倍的钱　－我不行
很简单的
苦差事我来做就好
我不能跟其他男人上床
我还爱着马西莫
别这么浪漫了
要务实一点
趁我们年轻，能捞尽量捞
- Hmm.
- LUCIA:
你需要钱才能做音乐
你很有才华
谢谢你，露西
Niente.
所以呢？
－你想做吗？　－好啦
我跟你一起去，但不能三人行
Mia.
米亚，他走了
（意语）
Non dimenticar
Means don't forget you are
＂意思是别忘记你的心，亲爱的＂
My darling...
走开
快一点啦
去别的地方拉吧
- Hmm?
- Mia.
－米亚，你超美的　－真的吗？
天啊，我看起来好像妓女
就是要这样
你疯了
才没有
No.
你很美
（意语）不懂你干吗‥
（意语）拜托，我需要这两个
Only just tonight dear
晚安，杭特夫妇
Good evening, Mr. and Mrs. Hunt.
－米凯尔
－欢迎
- Ah, Mikael. This is my wife, Tanya.
- Welcome.
这是内人谭雅
Nice to meet you, Mrs.
Tanya. Hi. Hi.
－幸会，谭雅夫人
－你好‥
你今天好吗？
我听了很多关于你的事情
How are you today?
- I heard a lot about you.
- Oh.
幸会，你今天过得好吗？
Nice to meet you.
How was your day today?
Oh, it was a... it was a...
It was a good day.
今天‥很愉快
One sec. Did you watch
the football today?
－失陪一下
－你看今晚的足球赛了吗？
No, well, my country has a whole
different kind of football.
没有，我们国家看的是另一种足球
我叫你留在房里
I told you to stay in the room.
我得吃饭啊
I had to eat.
Oh, my God.
He's gonna flip the fuck out.
天啊，他一定会气疯
What are you... Shit!
Here. Hold that.
糟糕
这样
她回来了
Anyway. Here she is.
Sorry. Shall we go to the table?
－我们入座好吗？
－当然，吃饭吧
- Yeah, why not? Let's eat.
- Please.
Okay. I'll take
you to the table.
－好
－我来带位，请跟我来
- Follow me, please.
- Oh, my God.
天啊
- Thanks, I love it.
- I got it, I got it.
＂（意语）要是我们分道扬镳＂
We just flew
all the way in from Los Angeles.
我们大老远从洛杉矶搭机过来
Just to be here in Sicily.
就为了来一趟西西里
Because we are Sicilian.
Are you Sicilian?
因为我们是西西里人
你是西西里人吗？
我是，我来自卡塔尼亚
- Yes, from Catania.
- Ah. Are you married?
你结婚了吗？
Dad, why don't you let her
put our order in
爸，先让她帮我们点餐吧
这样我才有酒喝
so I can get a drink?
My son is a big muckity-muck
in Hollywood,
我儿子是好莱坞的大人物
- so he's very impatient.
- I'll bring you your drinks.
所以他没什么耐心
－我送喝的过来
－谢谢你
- Thank you.
- Thanks. Sorry.
抱歉
Thank you.
谢谢
- Dad, you gotta knock it off.
- Oh. What's the problem?
－爸，别再这样了
－有什么问题吗？
What are you doing?
I mean, what's... the point?
你在做什么？
这有什么意义吗？
Flirting is one
of the pleasures of life.
调情是人生的一大享受
Do you actually think
you have a chance
你真的觉得自己有机会吗？
with any of these women?
别这么失礼
Oh, don't be rude.
I'm just saying,
you're 80 years old.
你都已经八十岁了
Well, I'm still a man.
And I get older and older,
但我还是男人
虽然我越来越老
but the women I desire
remain young.
但我依旧渴望年轻的女人
Natural, right?
这很自然吧？
你一定感同身受
You can relate to that.
Can you still get...
你还能‥
- Or... Do you still get...
- What? Hard?
－什么，变硬吗？
－勃起吗？
Erections?
Sure. Like that.
－当然，跟拳头一样硬
－真的吗？
- Really?
- Albie.
－阿尔比
－你还会‥
Do you still, like, jerk off?
打手枪吗？
Doctors say you need
to release once a day...
医生说每天至少要释放一次
- otherwise you get backed up.
- Wait a second.
否则会囤积
等一下
Doctors say you need
to jerk off once a day?
－医生叫你每天打手枪一次？
－没错‥
- That's right. That's right.
- Which doctors say that?
哪个医生说的？
You need to drain the sack.
你得释放精液
- They say that?
- Mm-hmm.
医生真的这么说？
没错，这是常识
Common knowledge.
God. It just seems like the body
天啊，我以为过了繁殖年龄
就不会有好色的念头了
would naturally stop
getting horny
once you're past the age
of procreation, you know?
－例如到五十岁就不会做了
－五十岁？
Like at 50, you would just stop.
Fifty? Fifty's not that old.
五十岁又没多老
- It just seems undignified.
- I'm still virile, by the way.
我只是觉得那样很不庄重
我还有生育力
还是能让女人怀孕
I could still impregnate
a woman.
- Oh.
- No girl
老人的下体
不该让年轻女生看到吧
should have to be exposed
to an old guy's junk.
It's not like it was ever
so beautiful to look at anyway.
下体本来就没有多好看
I mean, it's a penis.
It's not a sunset.
阴茎又不是夕阳美景
Hookers.
是妓女
Really?
真的吗？
Oh, yeah.
没错
Looks like a couple of locals.
那两位感觉是当地人
Buona sera.
（意语）晚安
Just because you're here
Come on, man.
You don't recognize a hooker?
拜托，你分不出妓女吗？
So innocent, man.
真是天真，跟大学时一样
Just like in college.
伊森是最早的非自愿独身者
Ethan was the original incel.
What are you talking about?
No, I wasn't.
你在说什么？
我才不是呢
Yeah, you were.
Come on, man.
拜托，你明明就是
我只是开玩笑‥
No, I'm... I'm kidding.
I'm kidding, man.
I'm joking, all right? Look,
you could have gotten laid.
你当时一定能上床
他长得很帅吧？
- He's a handsome guy, right?
- Yeah.
－对
－看看你的脸蛋
Jesus Christ, look at you.
You're a handsome guy.
I'd do ya.
你很帅，是我就愿意跟你做
You're just such
a workhorse, man.
你只是忙着工作，老是待在房间
You never came out of your room.
Well, he's still like that.
现在还是一样
Okay, I think we should
split the arugula salad
我们应该合点
一份芝麻叶沙拉，一份甜菜沙拉
and the beet salad,
and then maybe get
the raviolo and the vitello.
意大利饺和小牛肉
I kinda wanted
to try the fish, but...
我想点鱼
- The whitefish?
- Yeah.
－白身鱼吗？
－对
Hmm.
No, I feel it'll be too fishy.
－我觉得鱼味太重了
－好吧
Okay.
I mean, it's whitefish,
it's pretty light.
白身鱼的鱼味并不重
It's not a very fishy fish.
Well, you can get it tomorrow.
We're gonna be here all week.
－你可以明天点，我们会待一周
－好吧‥
Okay. All right. Yeah.
Or we can have the whitefish.
Let's do it.
不然我们点白身鱼好了
I just don't like it
when it's too fishy.
我只是不喜欢太浓的鱼味
- Mm-hmm. Yeah, me too.
- Yeah, sure.
－当然
－我也一样
- Great.
- Great. It sounds good.
－很好
－听起来不错
Let's do it.
那就点吧
- Neat.
- Wine, people?
要点酒吗？
Yes.
要点什么酒？
- What do we want?
- I like white.
我喜欢白酒
我也是，我偏好白酒
Me too. I prefer white.
Non dimenticar
Although you travel far
My darling
＂亲爱的＂
It's my heart you own
＂你会拥有我的心
所以我会单独等待＂
So I'll wait alone
＂别忘记你的心＂
Non dimenticar
I don't know
what they're clapping for.
不知道他们在鼓掌什么
那个歌手糟糕透了
This singer's abominable.
我觉得还行啊
Sounded okay to me.
Go to your room.
走‥
Go. Your room.
Your room.
You're not feeling sluggish
or not concentrating?
你会觉得疲惫或无法专心吗？
Head is fine.
And it's not gonna happen again.
我的头没事
我不会再跌倒了
不过是跌倒而已，没事的
It was a little fall, nothing.
－你今天还是跟阿尔比一起睡吧
－好吧
You should sleep
with Albie anyway.
All right.
How was your caprese?
你的卡布里沙拉怎么样？
Hmm.
I was told that the cheese here
was made by a blind nun
听说这里的起司
是瞎眼修女在地下室做的
in a basement.
我走了
注意安全
这不是你奶奶经营的民宿
这可是五星级饭店
你懂吗，帕吉欧？
Hey!
她不见了
这婊子跑得真快
You know,
I... I think you're fine.
这样吧
我觉得你没事了
You... you didn't hit your head
that hard or... you know,
你头的伤没那么严重
所以我先走了‥
so, I should...
I'm just gonna go.
So, I'll see you in the morning.
早上见了
- Good night.
- Good night, Nonno. Sleep well.
－晚安
－晚安，爷爷
祝你一觉好眠
Buona sera.
（意语）晚安
（意语）谢谢
Grazie.
表演还喜欢吗？
喜欢
你唱得很好
Oh, grazie.
（意语）谢谢
你朋友丢下你？
她很快就回来了
我叫乔赛佩
我叫米亚
我也是歌手
是吗？
我的梦想是当音乐人
表演自己写的歌
你能以此为生真是太棒了
对我来说很难想像
必须出类拔萃，才能在这种地方工作
我会弹钢琴
Hmm.
我得付钱吗？
要多少？
Hmm?
我得领多少钱？
No. No, no, no, no.
不是
不对‥
你搞错了
我知道你来这里做什么
我们可以去一个安静的地方
Mm-hmm.
我只要在午夜前回家就行了
Hmm?
She was definitely
more talkative by the pool.
她在游泳池的时候话比较多了
And at dinner,
she was actually kinda nice.
晚餐时甚至可以说是和颜悦色
Well...
now that he's loaded,
现在伊森发了
do you think
he regrets marrying such a dud?
你觉得他会后悔
自己娶了一个丑女吗？
小卡，我想再跟他们视讯一次
Cam, I wanna FaceTime
them again.
- What?
- Please?
－什么？
－拜托啦
Honey, come on.
We just hung up.
老婆，我们才刚挂电话呢
我知道，但我好想艾玛
I know, but I miss Emma so much.
I know.
Of course you do.
我知道你很想她
但重点不在这里，重点是‥
But that's not the point,
all right?
The point is...
we're in Italy, honey. Okay?
我们在意大利，老婆
好吗？
Mm-Hmm.
We're on vacation.
－我们两个人在度假
－对啊
- Just you and me.
- Yeah.
- We need to enjoy it.
- Okay.
我们必须好好享受
－好喔
－就我跟我的宝贝
- Just me and my baby.
- Ooh.
- And you know what that means.
- What?
－你懂我的意思
－什么意思？
- You need something.
- Mm-hmm.
你需要某个东西
You need...
你需要‥搔痒攻击
- a tickle attack.
- No!
No!
－小卡，住手‥
－我骗到你了
- Please! Stop!
- Tickle, tickle, tickle. I got you!
小卡，不要‥
No, stop it!
Hey, hey!
Is he hurting her?
他在伤害她吗？
卡麦隆，不要‥
- No! No...
- Hey! Tickle attack!
搔痒攻击
Monkey man, monkey man!
No.
不是啦
Thanks for making more
of an effort.
谢谢你为我努力
I mean, yeah, they kind
of live in a bubble, but...
他们确实活在自己的世界
they're fun, right?
但他们很有趣，对吧？
－他们不投票耶，伊森
－我懂，搞什么？
They don't vote, Ethan.
I know. What the fuck?
They don't read the news.
－连新闻都不看
－他们根本不阅读吧
They don't read.
It's like,
what do they even talk about?
他们都聊什么？
Is that what happens
难道人有钱太久
大脑就会萎缩吗？
when you're rich for too long,
your brain just atrophies?
I mean, they seem happy.
他们似乎很快乐
No way. It's a front.
不可能
那只是表面
It's good to have, you know,
diverse friends, I guess.
有不一样的朋友是件好事
我觉得啦
Yeah, I think
we're their diverse friends.
我才是他们不一样的朋友吧
Their White-passing
diverse friends.
他们＂算得上白人＂的朋友
Yeah, you're right.
你说得对
When we came up here
to get the suit,
我们上来拿泳裤的时候
he just took all
of his clothes off
他在房间里脱个精光
in the middle of the room.
Like, naked.
全身裸体
And then you...
Like, where were you?
那你当时在那里？
In the bathroom.
浴室
Doesn't seem that weird.
这没有很怪吧
Just getting changed.
只是换个衣服而已
Baby, come here!
Baby, come on.
No!
Wow.
All right, look.
我现在不想谈这个，好吗？
Look. Listen,
I don't wanna fucking talk
about this right now, okay?
Yes, I'm going to. Yeah.
This is not the time.
对‥
现在不是时候
Yes.
好‥
Fuck.
该死
- Hi.
- Hey.
Who are you talking to?
－你在跟谁说话？
－工作的事，是巴伯
It's work. It's Bob.
Oh, Bob. Well,
why were you whispering?
巴伯，那你干吗轻声细语的？
I... I thought you were trying
to get ready for bed.
我以为你准备要睡觉了
Oh, well. Guess what?
你猜怎么着？
- Huh?
- Look what I found.
你看我发现了什么
- Oh, okay.
- Two macaroons!
好的
两颗蛋白杏仁饼
- Yeah, great.
- Yeah.
－太好了
－我确实只吃了三颗
I really did only eat three.
太好了，但你晚餐吃了整份奶酪
Oh. Well, great.
You had a whole
panna cotta at dinner.
Well, eat them,
'cause you wanted 'em.
吃吧，你刚才不是想吃吗？
I don't want them now.
我现在不想吃
为什么？
拿去吧，很好吃喔
Why? Yeah, take them,
they're good.
Tanya, I just brushed my teeth.
I'm on the phone.
谭雅，我刚刷牙
而且电话讲到一半
Uh, Bob, I gotta go...
巴伯，我得挂了
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
－给你
－谢谢
干杯‥
- Cheers.
I went down to the dock
when your boat arrived.
我到码头看你搭的船进港
I wanted to see
what you looked like.
我想看看你的长相
What'd you think?
你觉得怎么样？
非常英俊
Very handsome.
Thank you.
谢谢你
And you're from Los Angeles.
而且你来自洛杉矶，太厉害了
It's amazing. I always dreamt
of going to Los Angeles.
去洛杉矶一直都是我的梦想
It is my dream.
Uh, I mean...
我是说‥
You should go.
你应该去看看
I don't have the money.
我没有钱
You seem like
a very nice person. Um...
你感觉是个好人
I'm just going through a lot
right now in my life.
我现阶段的人生有很多困难
So, it's... it's, um...
所以‥
hard for me
to make conversation right now.
现在很不会跟人聊天
But you are very, uh, beautiful.
但你很美
I'm glad you're here.
我很高兴你来了
Allora...
（意语）那么‥
待续
谢谢观赏